[narrator] There's a moment
where you're out on a golf course
and the sun is sitting
just right in the sky.
where if you blur your eyes.
heaven and earth meet.
And the world as... [chuckles]
...you know it ceases to exist.
and everything fades
into the bend of a fairway up ahead
and the gentle break
of a green in the distance.
Doesn't matter if you're a beginner
or the number one player in the world.
At that moment.
golf stops just being a game played with
a little white ball and a four-inch cup.
The course becomes a cathedral.
and you become baptized by a higher power.
Now some guys can harness that power.
bend it to their will.
and glimpse the center of the cosmos.
[chuckling] But they're the rare few.
The greats. The GOATs.
Now let's be honest. most people
don't have what it takes to tap into that.
But a guy like you. with that physique.
that's just God-given.
Listen. some can. some can't.
But you. my friend.
you're built for this game.
My wife says I'm too chunky
to play anything.
- Chunky?
- Yeah.
Are you kidding me?
Is that the word she used?
Okay. with all due respect to your wife.
that's not what I'm looking at.
What I see is power.
[stammering] I don't work out.
Yeah. of course you don't.
'Cause you're country strong.
You're not getting that in a gym.
And by the way. gym bodies break down.
If a tornado blows through here
and I'm trapped under a log.
you know who I'm calling? You.
Here. try this.
Actually. even you
I can't start with this.
Let me...
Let me start you with this guy right here.
No. no. no. wait. wait. wait. What's...
What's... What's up with that one?
The PXG Proto. but I can't put
a lot of people into this club
because they just can't handle it.
- [stammers]
- I could try it.
[sighs]
Come on. I'm here. Let me try it.
I can see this guy is not gonna
take no for an answer. Go ahead.
- Oh. wow. that's really nice.
- Yeah.
But I think you better work your way up.
No. no. no. Just let me take a swing.
Okay. I feel like
you should sign a waiver.
Proceed at your own risk.
Yeah. I like the weight.
Whoa!
Goddamn it. are you kidding me?
I think we got a new mayor of Pound Town.
That felt good.
Yeah. it looked good.
Okay. how much?
Twelve hundred.
- Oh.
- I know. it's pricey.
But the Proto has
internal twin vertical bars
that concentrates all that G
into the face of the club.
I'm feeling this club.
[exhales sharply] Some clubs choose you.
It's kinda like King Arthur with ol'
Excalibur. just pulling it from the stone.
[chuckles]
- All right. let's do it.
- Fantastic!
Sally. can we ring Dale up for a Proto.
and let's throw in a box
of the Pro Vs on the house.
Dale. I'm telling you. with that body and
that club... [whispers] you're dangerous.
[knocking]
- Knock-knock.
- [sighs] What is it. Pryce?
Marv. I just sold a Proto
and a Callaway walker.
Twenty-four hundred.
I was hoping I could maybe get
a little advance on that commission.
- Yeah. it'll be in your check next week.
- Well. that's just it.
I was thinking maybe I could wet my beak
today 'cause I'm a little light this week.
[chuckles]
You're a little light this week?
- Yeah.
Just a couple hundred dollars.
You still owe me from last week.
- I know. But Marv. come on.
- Yeah.
Don't you want to keep
your top salesman happy?
You're not my top salesman.
Well. I'm your favorite. I like to think.
Come on. it's just a few bucks
and it gets me out of your office.
- Okay.
- I should've led with that. right?
You should've led with that.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
- You said a couple hundred?
- Yes.
There you go.
Could you leave the balls. please?
- These are freebies.
- Just leave the balls. man.
- Thank you. Yeah.
- I could sell these.
Every shot's a pigeon for me today.
- Get outta here.
- Bye.
[engine starts]
[engine revs]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- [shrieks]
- [gasps] Jesus Christ.
- You scared the shit out of me.
- You scared me.
[chuckling] What are you doing here?
I'm measuring rooms.
We're selling the house.
Pryce. this place is a wreck.
- [sighs] It's not a wreck. it's...
- [chuckles. stammers]
- [clattering]
- Sorry.
You know. the garbage comes
every Thursday morning.
All this stuff. it can go in a bag.
and then that big. noisy blue truck
that comes. it takes it away.
Okay. yeah. I wondered what
those guys were doing every week.
And. Pryce?
[breathes heavily] Those are wet.
- What happened to the garbage disposal?
- It lost a fight with a wooden spoon.
But it went down swinging.
I mean. it shredded that spoon.
But listen. you were saying
something about selling the house.
And I think what we agreed
is we were gonna mull it over.
- No.
- Yeah.
The mulling is over.
We've been divorced for years.
I am mulled out.
You can't sell the house.
All my stuff is here.
- I live here.
- [chuckles] No. you're squatting here.
I said you could stay until
you found a place of your own.
Honey. that was two years ago.
This is happening.
[sighs]
I have a client dinner.
Hmm.
The pool. Pryce...
[chuckles] ...it looks like a swamp.
It's probably a biohazard.
Would you please clean it?
Yes. I'm adding it to the list.
right after the disposal.
- I fear for that list.
- Don't.
Don't forget we have to meet
with the lawyers in the afternoon.
I know. I'm well aware of that meeting.
Tell me again the time.
- 3:15.
Just double-checking. Got it.
- [inhales sharply. clears throat]
- Clean the pool.
[switch clicks]
[groans]
Ay ay ay.
[sighs]
There you are. my little friend.
I was worried sick about you.
Where's your little sidekick?
[coughs]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[groans]
[groaning]
[grunts]
[birds chirping]
[snoring]
[theme song playing]
[Pryce] Here we are on the 18th green
as Mildred Nussbaum lines up
the most important putt of her life.
I'm telling you.
this gal plays with a swagger that's
caught everyone off guard this season.
- Swagger. [chuckles]
- [whooshes]
- [chuckles]
- Nailed that fucker. [chuckles]
- Better than most. Better than most.
- [whooshes]
Jesus. did you hear that?
I can barely hear you.
Wait right here. Mrs. Nussbaum.
I'll be right back.
Now that's how you pepper a steak.
Yeah. we were down at the putting green.
I thought somebody
was firing a rifle down here.
You know. you're cupping
your wrist just a little bit.
If you close that club face.
you'll put an extra ten yards on it.
Not that you need any more distance.
I'm not into older guys.
but I'm flattered.
Good to know. What's your name?
Go fuck yourself.
Is that a family name?
Aren't younger people supposed to annoy
older people. not the other way around?
No. it actually works both ways.
Hey. twenty bucks says you can't put it
within five feet of that 200 yard marker.
[clears throat]
Or just go ahead and hit it.
Hold on. hold on.
[stammers] Give me a chance
to win my money back.
Double or nothing.
The 250 marker.
Okay.
Are you kidding me?
Who taught you how to swing?
Hundred bucks. I hit the 320 marker.
There is no 320 marker.
Sure there is.
[thuds]
That's 320.
- [club owner] Hey!
- Oh. shit.
Get the hell out of here.
I'm calling the cops next time!
You know him?
He said his name was Go Fuck Yourself.
- I'm pretty sure it's an alias.
- Little shit.
Works over at Decatur Market.
I catch him shagging balls up here
all the time. Doesn't pay.
Keeps dinging up my shed.
[sighs] That used to be a beautiful shed.
- He's hit that before?
- A lot.
[pen clicking]
I'm sorry.
[phone rings]
- Hi. [exhales sharply]
- Hello.
[Pryce clears throat]
- [sighs]
- Hi.
- Where's your lawyer?
- Well. we had a couple of disagreements.
Specifically over his fee and my desire
to pay. so I'm gonna represent myself.
No. Mr. Cahill.
I highly advise against that.
Okay. well. thank you for your counsel.
I have consulted with my counsel. me.
and I object.
- [sighs]
- To what?
I don't know. what he just said.
You always said I'd be a good lawyer.
Mmm. no. That's not what I said.
Yeah. you did.
- I said you are very argumentative.
- Well. I took that as a compliment.
- [Pryce's ex-wife] It's not a compliment.
- Listen. what are we here to discuss?
If it's to go over
what a disappointment I am.
I think we've covered that ad nauseam.
[smacks lips] Yes.
Uh. although the divorce
has been finalized.
there's still the outstanding matter
of the family home.
- Yeah.
- [lawyer] Mm-hmm.
What am I looking at?
Uh. that is a property transfer agreement.
It conveys any interest you still have
in any shared property to Amber-Linn.
Overruled.
[stammers] You can't overrule--
Well. you need me to sign that
in order to sell the house.
I'm not gonna do it.
Checkmate. Your move. Sosa.
Look... [stammers]
...we actually don't need this. right?
This just means that
we don't have to file a 736. so fine.
A which... A 73-who?
- A 736.
- What is that?
It's something that
your lawyer would've known.
[lawyer] It means court.
It is when a judge will enforce
the provisions you've already agreed to.
I don't want to sell.
Pryce. don't.
Mr. Cahill. if you stand in the way
of the sale of this house.
you're in for a rude awakening.
Well. you're in contempt. okay?
That's contempt.
No. it's... it's not.
Yes. your tone is contemptuous.
We're not in a courtroom.
Okay? I feel like you guys
are ganging up on me.
- I'm being mean.
- You get me into this weird.
- brown little drab room...
- [lawyer] It's not drab.
...where dreams go to die.
It's really hot in here.
He's throwing bizarre
sequences of numbers at me.
- One number. It's 736.
- I'm freaking out.
My chair is not as high as yours.
- Then we will file it in court.
- Then raise your chair.
- There's a tiny lever under it.
- Pryce... Everyone. can we just. like...
Please. Please.
Let's just...
Let's just press the reset button. okay?
I'm happy to.
Look. I should've told you this last
night. and I'm really sorry that I didn't.
I chickened out.
But we have a buyer for the house.
And I will give you
$75.000 after it sells.
You can start over.
get back on your feet again.
Start fresh.
I don't want you to sell it.
I know you don't.
But we can't keep hanging onto this thing.
- [sighs]
- [Amber-Linn] I wanna move on.
You need to move on.
It's been a long time.
I wanna see you start living again.
[sighs] I am living.
No. what you're doing. it's...
[sighs]
What you're doing
in that house is not living.
I don't wanna spend the rest of my life
watching you waste yours.
[Amber-Linn] Please.
Honey.
I'm not gonna let you sell it.
- [sighs]
- Court's adjourned.
We're not in court.
[sighs]
[music plays]
Hey. Hey!
I know who you are.
You're that golfer. aren't you?
- Cahill. Bryce Cahill.
- Pryce.
- [bar patron 1] Right. Am I right?
- Yep. that's me.
- Good eye.
- Oh. Goddamn it. I knew it. I knew it.
- Used to call you Stick. right?
- Mmm.
This guy was a big pro golfer.
on television and everything.
No shit. I watched you.
That tournament where
you did that thing. remember?
When was that?
Uh. it's hard to say.
You're painting
a real picture there. chief. Uh...
This fucking guy. Twelfth hole.
Big tourney.
Sawgrass. I think. maybe like. uh.
2009 probably.
Shanks one into the lake
and just melts down.
Full psychotic break on live TV.
[chuckles] It was insane.
Threw his clubs in the water.
Kicked the shit out of Clark Ross.
- [chuckles]
- The ReadySafe Insurance guy?
[bar patron 1] Yeah. that guy.
He was his playing partner.
Just laid him out in the locker room.
That was you. right. buddy?
[chuckles]
Man. I bet it kills you
to see those commercials. huh?
Actually. you know what's killing me
is I'm not able to give
this frosty the proper focus.
If you can just let me relax. thanks.
[bar patron 1] Uh-huh.
I bet you can't even look at a club
after a train wreck like that. right?
[chuckles]
Why don't you shut up?
Seriously.
I tried to be polite. but just back off.
All right. was just talking. buddy.
No... [stammers] ...I'm talking.
You're slurring.
Hundred bucks says you can't
drain a putt right now. right here.
I got clubs in my trunk. man.
I don't play anymore.
Two hundred bucks says you hose one
from the bar to the kitchen. pal.
Go away.
Please. please. I'm asking nicely.
Come on. super sport.
You were a big pro once. man.
This is an easy putt.
Flat lie.
There's no lake around to freak you out.
[bar patrons laugh]
Five hundred.
Okay. He can count.
Do-Do you know your letters also?
Thousand bucks. champ.
Thousand bucks.
Do you still got
anything left in the tank.
or are you just some broke down never-was?
[bar patron 2] I'll take that bet.
Shut this asshole up.
[bar patron 1] Yeah. shut me up. Cahill.
Shut me up.
There he is.
It's an important putt for Cahill.
After he triple bogeyed his entire life.
You don't got this.
Don't freak out. Stick.
Don't choke.
[all] Ah.
- [clamors]
- God!
Yes!
Yes.
Oh. my God!
Jesus! That was easy.
I mean. man.
that guy couldn't wait to jump in.
That was crazy.
Two. three. four...
Here's five hundred.
Thanks.
[sighs]
[chuckles] Yeah.
- [sighs]
- What's the matter with you?
Uh. you know. you-you could
ease up a little on the whole
"Pryce Cahill. broke down failure."
- What are you talking about?
- It's just...
[stammers] You don't have to be so.
I don't know. honest.
Look. man. I mean.
those details matter. okay?
- Yeah. they matter.
- I gotta... I gotta keep the--
Well. if the details matter
then get 'em right.
You said. you know.
"broke down never-was."
That's not right.
"Broke down has-been."
I don't like it. but you could say that.
All right. look. I'm just trying
to keep the hustle fresh. you know?
- You kept it fresh.
- I didn't wanna do this tonight.
You're the one who needed the cash again.
I mean... [stammers] ...there's a million
things I could be doing right now.
Name two things.
And don't say crossword puzzles
or watching that idiotic show.
Hey. you know. don't knock the housewives.
- All right? [stammers]
- I will knock it
- 'cause it gets you negative.
- Those ladies have a lot going on. Pryce.
Yeah. and I can see.
That's where you get stuff like saying.
"Triple bogeyed your life."
I know. I was playing a character.
We're doing a hustle.
You were playing a character.
- You could've made the shot. You--
- I know. but you're playing it too good.
Maybe you're just
being a little sensitive.
I am.
Well. look. I'm sorry... [stammers]
...you're feeling this way. all right?
- Thanks. [sighs]
- Yeah.
Can we go?
[Pryce] I mean. she's right.
I have wasted the last. God knows.
how many years of my life.
Yeah. all right.
But if you keep looking in the rearview
you're gonna swerve off the road.
[Pryce] No. I know.
And it isn't even Amber-Linn
kicking me out that put the whammy on me.
It's really... It was that guy at the bar.
The guy who bet on me.
I mean. did you see him?
He was so confident.
Like. that guy really believed in me.
- I wanna get his number and hang out.
- [scoffs]
Like. what was he seeing?
'Cause I look in the mirror.
I would not bet on that guy.
Jesus Christ.
you gotta cut yourself some slack. man.
[sighs]
I don't know. things were supposed to
be different for me. Mitts.
[stammers] So what?
You know.
Francine and I were gonna
go to all the national parks
in this Winnebago before she died.
Never got the chance.
Shit happens.
You know that better than anyone.
The question you gotta ask
yourself now is what's next?
What's next?
That's my pep talk.
That was your pep talk?
It's all I got.
Five minutes. Housewives.
Okay.
- [Mitts] Come on. You watch it. it gets...
- I'll see you in there.
...gets you out of your head.
[Pryce] What's next?
[Mitts] What's next?
[door closes]
...somebody who works here. he's. like.
maybe about this high.
So your name's not "Go Fuck Yourself."
- It's Santi.
- What?
- Rebecca told me in the front.
- [Santi] What are you doing here?
- Are you some kind of stalker?
- No. no. no. no. no.
- I'm just a golfer.
- Oh. you sure?
Because you followed me to where I work.
and we're total strangers.
- So... Yeah.
- I get it. Here.
- Pryce Cahill.
- [sighs]
"The Pryce is right." What does that mean?
Branding. Always be branding.
I get that you're Pryce. but what's right?
Like. what are you...
What are you saying is "right"?
Clever play on words.
- Don't overthink it.
- Okay. All right.
Hey. 320 marker.
Are you kidding me?
What a shot.
Bet's a bet.
How long have you been in love?
- What?
- With golf.
I'm not in love with golf.
I don't even like it.
Oh. really? You're just sneaking out
onto the driving range for exercise?
Come on. anyone who hits the ball
the way you do has gotta be in love.
Okay. I get it. It's like a girl.
You don't wanna say you like her
until you know if she likes you.
- What are you talking about. man?
- Let me save you some time.
She likes you. She is way into you.
I used to think she liked me.
but she is in love with you.
You ever play competitively?
I'm not interested.
[stammers] You gotta love her
while she's there.
Because when she's gone. she is gone.
Trust me.
- [manager] What the hell is going on?
- Oh. shit.
You're not on break.
and who the fuck are you?
Sorry. I just needed Santi for a bit.
I don't give a fuck what you need.
A lot of swearing.
Isn't there. like. a no swearing
around customers policy?
You know what? Get the fuck out
of my stock room. or I will bounce you.
I'll bounce myself.
Rebecca was really nice.
[balloon squeaking]
[clears throat. sighs]
Is Elena Wheeler here?
[high-pitched] She's in the back.
[clerks chuckling]
- [clerk 2] You sound like a baby.
- [clerk 1. normal] I am a baby.
- [Pryce] Excuse me.
- Hi.
Hi. are you Santi's mother?
Oh. my God. What happened? Qué pasó?
No. no. no. he's fine. Sorry. [chuckles]
I got your name from Rebecca at his work.
Uh. my name's Pryce.
I just wanted to talk to you about...
[clerk 1 high-pitched]
Suck my dick. [laughs]
- [Pryce] You know. I saw--
- Kevin.
How many times do I have to tell you
to knock it off... con el ...helium?
The shit's expensive.
- [high-pitched] Sorry. Elena.
- [Elena] And you know what?
There's 30 Captain America tablecloths
on aisle six on the floor.
Go pick 'em up.
- [Kevin. clerk 2 laughing]
- Sorry. who are you again?
My name's Pryce. I'm a golf pro.
And I saw your son at Lennox.
At the golf course?
Yeah. I was watching him hit.
And. I mean.
what he was doing with the ball.
the way he was swinging.
you can't teach that.
And that comes from someplace else.
- You know. from... [chuckles]
- Yeah.
Um. I'm sorry.
My son hasn't touched a golf club
since he was 14 years old.
Well. the manager says
he sneaks out there all the time
on the driving range.
so he's definitely hitting.
Anyway. I'd like to work with him.
You know. maybe even take him on the road.
Try to qualify him
for the US Amateur in August.
Yeah. okay. no problem. strange man.
Just have him back before Christmas.
- [Pryce chuckles]
- [chuckles]
I get it. I'm sorry. I know this must seem
like I'm coming out of left field.
but I was a professional golfer.
Member of the Ryder Cup team
a long time ago.
So. I've been lucky enough
to see some great golfers.
And your son. well.
he made a real impression on me.
So. I'd cover all travel expenses.
I would pay tournament fees.
And if he does well there's. you know...
there's a real financial upside.
He's got a lot working for him.
And I know it's a lot to take in.
but here's my card.
and just think about it.
- "The Pryce is right."
- Yes. a little saying.
[chuckles] It's ridiculous.
- No. it's good. Thank you.
- Yeah. that's great.
Oy. [chuckles] Be careful.
[chuckles]
[dogs barking]
[speaking Spanish]
- [knocks on door]
- Santi.
- Yeah?
- Can I open the door?
You already opened it.
[sighs] How was work?
Whatever. it was fine. [sighs]
[clicks tongue] You know.
a man came to see me today.
Said he met you at Lennox.
[sighs] Are you serious?
The weird stalker guy came to see you?
I thought you were finished with golf?
You didn't tell me you were playing again.
I'm not playing again.
[groans] He said he saw you swing.
He was impressed.
I was just shagging some balls.
It's not a big deal. Okay?
- [in Spanish] Could you close the door?
- [in English] No. no.
[in Spanish] Give me a sec.
[in English] Hold on.
So this guy. I looked him up. He's legit.
He wants to take you
on the road this summer.
Thinks you could do good
at the US Amateur.
said there could be some money in it.
I already told him.
"I'm not interested. man."
I told him that.
So. I just wanna be alone right now. okay?
No. I wanna talk about this.
I'm worried about you.
I haven't seen you happy in a long time.
and I just think this is something that...
- That you should think about.
- I'm fucking done with golf.
- Mami. I'm not doing that again.
- [sighs] Okay...
[shushes] ...don't use that tone with me.
I mean. why would you want me
to play again after what happened?
Because the last time I saw you smile
was on a golf course.
- Geez.
- I know what it means to you.
Golf used to make you happy.
[stammers] Well. he ruined it for me.
No. golf doesn't have to be what it was
before when your dad was here.
It can be whatever you want it to be.
[sighs]
[stammers] Well. go...
go and find out how serious this guy is.
Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. yeah. yeah.
- [knocks on door]
- [dogs barking]
[Elena speaking Spanish]
- [Pryce] Hi.
- [claps. speaking Spanish]
- Uh-oh.
- Sorry. they're loud but they don't bite.
- Okay.
- [speaking Spanish]
- Welcome.
- Thanks for meeting me.
Glad there's some openness to the idea.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
And-And before we get started.
let me just say again.
I could not believe any more strongly
in your son's talent.
You did a great job.
Thank you.
I saw your YouTube clip.
[sucks teeth]
Yeah. [chuckles]
And? [chuckles]
Did you ever play again after that?
[inhales sharply] Um. no. not really.
It was kinda hard to come back
from something like that.
And what happened?
Uh...
life.
Yeah.
- Okay. here's the deal.
- Let's hear it.
- You pay for travel. for both of us.
- Okay. For... For both?
Both.
You cover all entry fees.
All the equipment.
- Okay.
- Mm-hmm.
And if this works out.
and if I know anything. the smart money
is on this not working out.
Oh. you never know.
But if it works out. we would go 70-30.
- 70-30?
- Mmm. On everything he makes.
[inhales deeply]
- Deal. I agree.
- Okay.
And you pay me $100.000.
[laughs]
Okay. you want that in crypto
or gold bullion?
Eh. no. I think cash. Cash is good.
And that would be before we hit the road.
I thought you were kidding.
Are you serious?
I mean. do I look like I have a spare 100K
laying around?
You were just saying the smart money's
on it not working out. and-- [stammers]
Well. yeah. and you were just saying
that you couldn't believe in him more.
- So...
- [stammers] That's true.
I-I... [sighs] I-It's just...
That's a lot of money.
Look. I just know how good my son is.
I mean... [speaking Spanish]
Come.
He stopped playing when he was 14.
but before that. he won everything.
Okay. and I have two more boxes over there
in the garage full like this.
- He won all these?
- He wins everything.
All the time. Everything.
I have our future to think about.
I can't go on some wild goose chase.
No.
[sighs] Who coached him?
His dad.
He did a good job. [chuckles]
Why'd he stop playing?
[sighs] His dad.
Oh. Where's his dad now?
[scoffs] If you find him. let me know.
[Mitts] I'm just saying.
it's a weak hustle.
No. no. no. it's not a hustle.
It's an opportunity.
An opportunity to what? Lose 100 grand?
I mean. you've got better odds
playing keno.
That's not true.
Oh. they just put more waffles out.
I'm full. but there's waffles.
- Why do you still do this?
- What are you talking about?
You think I'm gonna let 287.000
DoubleTree points go to waste?
Stop it. stop it.
There's a whole buffet up there.
- Get some of the fiesta ranchero sauce.
- Mitts. listen.
Okay. Listen to me.
If I don't do this. what am I gonna do?
I didn't turn out.
Let's be honest.
I've been spinning my wheels for years.
And I am nowhere.
Okay.
You know. this kid's not gonna fix
what happened. right?
I didn't say it would.
I understand that.
But maybe it's a chance
to leave something behind
other than a YouTube clip
of the worst day of my life.
Here's the thing.
You know zero about this kid.
Okay. fine. he can nuke it off the tee.
but you haven't even seen his whole game.
- Mitts. I have a feeling. all right?
- Yeah.
Look. this game. it takes
and it takes and it takes from me.
Finally. the other day it taps me
on the shoulder. and I turn.
"Now what? Now what are you
gonna strip away from me?"
Only it didn't want anything.
It actually had its hands out like this.
Holding a beautiful blue Tiffany's box.
And I take it. and I open it up.
and guess what's inside?
The kid.
The kid is in the box.
Are-Are you on mushrooms right now?
No. I'm not on mushrooms.
I'm saying the game
is finally giving me something back.
And it's about time.
Because it owes me.
You were my caddy for 15 years.
it owes you too.
[sighs]
Right?
Where are you gonna get 100 grand?
Mikey D. Pryce Cahill.
How are you. amigo?
Hey. I got a quick question for you.
How would you like to get rich?
Yes. $100.000 is a lot of money.
But what would you say if we were getting
in on the ground floor
of the next Tiger Woods?
Hello. Steve?
Carla. Carla. look. can I just say
one thing in my defense. please?
This kid has more natural talent
than any golfer I've ever seen.
It's a very simple plan. Doug.
We take him on the road.
and we turn this kid into a gold mine.
Listen. I fell off a Bird scooter. okay?
That's why you hadn't heard from me.
I know there are no sure things.
Okay. well. then call it a loan if...
Hello?
[grunting]
[grunts] Okay. come on.
Let's go. Pryce.
Put a little extra cash in your pocket.
Spoil Rachel.
Maybe take her to the Bahamas.
[person] Rachel and I broke up.
I'm living with my dad again.
Well. take him to the Bahamas.
Oh. I'm sure I could still dial a phone.
but it's hard if you've broken an arm
and you're depressed.
I didn't wanna bring you down.
And. Carla... Carla?
It's not a boondoggle. believe me.
[chuckles]
I've spent my life on boondoggles.
This is anything but a boondoggle.
[stammers] Come... [sighs] Really?
[sighs]
I don't know why someone would have
one bathroom with a four bedroom house.
Can I call you right back
because a Bible salesman
just walked into my office?
Okay. okay. thanks.
Why are you wearing a tie?
Because I'm here in an official capacity.
and I got a business proposition for you.
What's this?
The thing for the house. I signed it.
So you're not gonna
be an asshole about it?
No. not this time.
So. what's the proposition?
Well. you know how you said
you'd give me 75K if I signed it?
- I need a little more.
- Uh. mmm. oh. hold on.
[groans. swallows]
I didn't wanna do a spit take.
- How much?
- Hundred thousand.
Why do you need $100.000?
Fresh start. like you said.
They're expensive these days.
[laughs]
Yes? I'll take that as a yes.
Come on. What is the angle. Pryce?
I can see this from a mile away.
- What is it?
- No. no. no.
I found a kid who swings a golf club
like a goddamn dream.
I wanna take him on the road.
You're stake horsing now.
Smart.
How much of our money have you lost
with your crazy fucking schemes?
No. this isn't a scheme.
I wanna help this kid.
I wanna teach him what I know.
It's never about somebody else. Pryce.
It's always about you.
Fine. let's say it's about me.
But it's also about this kid.
And you should see this kid
because he is great.
No. It's not gonna happen.
[sighs] Come on. you said if I signed it.
you'd help me start over.
Yeah. I thought it would be for
a down payment for a condo or something.
I know. but this...
Come on. this is so much better than that.
No. I'm not doing it.
Honestly. I swear. if you saw this kid.
I think you would understand.
- I don't have time for this.
- Let me show you how good he is.
- No.
- [stammers] Fifteen minutes.
- I don't have 15 minutes.
- Well. let me prove it to you.
- No. I'm not giving you 100 grand.
- Good.
I don't want you to give it to me
unless you see what I see.
I'm not giving it to you.
And I'm going to be late
for a walk-through.
Please. 15 minutes.
- Hey. Rebecca. Is Santi back there?
- Yes. he is.
Great.
Santi. hey!
- No. no. You cannot be here.
- No. no. I need you to come with me.
- Just two minutes. That's it.
- You have no sense of boundaries.
- [stammers] I'm working. I can't--
- Please.
Front parking lot. Just come with me.
All I need you to do is swing a club.
Maybe change your life forever.
What? Wait.
Hey. what are you doing
in my stock room again?
He's in the middle of a shift.
He's taking his break.
You get a smoke break. right?
Or whatever your generation needs.
Like a mental health time-out?
- Listen. asshole. I don't know who you--
- Again with the cussing.
- It's just lazy.
- [chuckles]
Santi. get back inside right now.
Okay. Santi.
you see that lovely woman over there.
That's Amber-Linn. my ex-wife.
So sorry about him.
I need you to show her how good you are.
One shot. Over the parking lot.
Through the trees
and into that yellow dumpster
at the end of the alley.
[laughs]
Okay. Santi. get back in the store.
Santi. look. you do this.
and I can get you and your mom the money.
You do this.
and you are off the manager track.
Big deal. So you lose out
on being this jerk in five years?
One shot. 175 yard baby draw.
through the gap in the trees.
Stick it in that yellow dumpster.
I told you. man.
I don't want to play golf anymore.
And I don't believe you. [chuckles]
Look. whatever happened to make you
stop playing this game. you gotta face it.
Trust me. I know what it's like
to put your life on hold
'cause something bad happened.
I've been doing it for years.
But you have a gift.
Okay. you were put here to play this game.
You and I both know that.
Don't turn your back on that.
Come on.
You take this swing
and it is over. young man.
No. you take this swing.
and it is just the beginning.
- Let's go.
- Yes. come on.
Okay. you're gonna wanna
open the club a little bit
- to make it through those trees.
- I got it.
Move it up just a little bit
in your stance.
Yeah. I know what I'm doing.
Hey. trust me.
[distorted] Yes! Come on!
There's two qualifiers
before the US Amateurs
and about a half dozen tournaments
in between.
But amateurs can get paid now.
Okay. this kid does well.
the sky's the limit.
What do you think?
[inhales deeply]
I think that when you want something
you are unstoppable.
- Yes.
- I had forgotten this side of you.
Don't forget that side.
You sure about this?
You've been saying I need to move on.
Maybe this is my chance.
It won't bring him back.
I know.
[cell phone buzzes]
- Ah.
- [cell phone buzzes]
- Hello.
- Hey. it's Pryce.
- I got the money.
- What?
You got the... [stammers] ...$100.000?
- Yep. We leave Saturday.
- This Saturday? I mean. so soon?
We gotta get him ready
for the Amateur in August.
[sighs] Right.
Okay. [sighs]
- Yeah. let's do it.
- Here we go.
- Let's do it.
- All right. see you.
[huffs]
- [laughs] Whoo!
- Yes!
[Pryce] I'm pulling back.
First strawberry. um...
[Pryce] Fondue. A little treat.
[Amber-Linn] All right. thank you.
- [Pryce] There we go.
- [Amber-Linn] Remember you... Ever...
[Pryce exhales sharply]
Hey. [yelps]
[laughs]
You're the one that took a nap. [laughs]
[groans]
[Pryce]
Ready for the Pryce Cahill hangover cure?
[Amber-Linn] Well.
I have the-the Pryce Cahill hangover so...
[laughs] I feel like it's only fair.
[Pryce] I wanna get your whole regimen
because you have such a beautiful smile.
Anything to show us
other than a beautiful smile?
Uh. no. nothing.
- [Pryce] Nothing?
- [Amber-Linn] Nothing at all.
[Pryce] What the heck?
We are getting close. aren't we?
Sometimes you can do this test. Oh. yeah.
- [Amber-Linn] It's like a melon.
- [Pryce] Three weeks. Three weeks.
- You think three?
- Yeah.
[Amber-Linn] Did it work?
He's asleep?
"No. Daddy. Stop filming me.
Stop filming me. Daddy."
- [baby coos]
- [Amber-Linn] Aw.
- [Pryce] Whoo!
- [Amber-Linn] There you go. Look at you!
- [baby cries]
- [Amber-Linn exclaims] Aw. No.
I wanna... [stammers] ...play golf.
[Pryce] Here. you have this one.
Little grip.
That one right there.
- I knew it!
- [Amber-Linn exclaims]
[chuckles] Ready. guys? Here we go.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday dear Jett! ♪
[video stops]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm